Indiana University Department of Radio and Television Chair's records, 1939-1963 C104
Indiana University Archives
- Administrative files, 1937-1962
  - Subject files, 1939-1963
    - Ziebarth, E.W., 1947 (Box 13)
    - Zimmer- McCaskey Advertising, 1946-1954 (Box 13)
- Radio and television shows, 1957-1961
  - "The Actor", undated (Box 13)
  - "Bathe in Brother's Blood", 1958 (Box 13)
  - "Beginning Shorthand", 1959 (Box 13)
  - "Challenge for Tomorrow", 1960 (Box 13)
  - "Conversation", 1959 (Box 13)
  - "Credit", 1959 (Box 13)
  - "Dance Forms", 1959 (Box 13)
  - "Drama Workshop", 1958 (Box 13)
  - "The Eve of the Election", 1958 (Box 13)
  - "First Aid", 1958 (Box 13)
  - "Focus on Debate", 1959 (Box 13)
  - "It's Your World", 1958 (Box 13)
  - "IU Serves You", 1959 (Box 13)
  - "University Spotlight # (Box 13)
    - #9, 1959 (Box 13)
    - #10, 1959 (Box 13)
    - #11, 1959 (Box 13)
    - #12, 1959 (Box 13)
    - #13, 1959 (Box 13)
    - #14, 1959 (Box 13)
    - #15, 1959 (Box 13)
    - #16, 1959 (Box 13)
    - #17, 1959 (Box 13)
    - #18, 1958 (Box 13)
    - #19, 1958 (Box 13)
    - #20, 1958 (Box 13)
    - #21, 1958 (Box 13)
    - #22, 1958 (Box 13)
    - #23, 1958 (Box 13)
  - "Literature of the Western World", 1958 (Box 13)
  - "Let's See", 1959-1961 (Box 13)
    - Completed Kine Transactions, 1958-1960 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 14)
    - Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 14)
    - Description material, 1958 (Box 14)
    - Future Borrowers of Kines, 1959-1960 (Box 14)
    - Present Borrowers of Kines, 1959-1961 (Box 14)
    - Series, 1957-1958 (Box 14)
    - Unconfirmed letters, 1958-1959 (Box 14)
  - "Man and His Gods", 1958 (Box 14)
  - "News in Perspective", 1959 (Box 14)
  - "Montage", 1958-1959 (Box 14)
  - "Music from Germany", 1956/1960 (Box 14)
  - "Nutrition Series", 1957 (Box 14)
  - "Once Upon a Time", undated (Box 14)
  - "Other People-Other Lands", 1959 (Box 14)
  - "Portraits for today", 1958 (Box 14)
  - Press conference, 1959 (Box 14)
  - "Preview", 1959 (Box 14)
  - "Problems in Everyday Speech" (Box 14)
    - Programs 1-4, 1947 and undated (Box 14)
    - Programs 5-8, undated (Box 14)
    - Programs 9-12, undated (Box 14)
    - Programs 13-16, undated (Box 14)
    - Programs 17-22, undated (Box 14)
    - Program 2 and correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 14)
    - Program 3, undated (Box 14)
  - "Rails of the Past", 1959 (Box 14)
  - "Serenade for Strings", 1959-1960 (Box 14)
  - "Students Look at the Compaign", 1960 (Box 14)
  - "Summer Conference", 1959 (Box 14)
  - "Sunday news & sports", 1958 (Box 14)
  - "Teaching in America", 1959 (Box 14)
  - "Verse and Reverse", 1958 (Box 14)
  - "The World Today", 1958-1959 (Box 14)
  - "World of Work", 1959 (Box 14)
  - "Your Congress Debates", 1959 (Box 14)
- Radio and television stations, 1943-1952
  - Station Contributions to I.U., 1948-1949 (Box 14)
  - Radio stations (miscellaneous) (Box 14)
    - 1950-1951 (two folders) (Box 14)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 14)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 14)
  - Elkhart City Schools, 1948 (Box 14)
  - Evansville Public Schools, 1949-1950 (Box 14)
  - Kansas State Department, 1948-1949 (Box 14)
  - KDKA, 1951-1952 (Box 14)
  - KIND, 1949-1950 (Box 14)
  - KJG, 1950 (Box 14)
  - KUOM, 1950-1951 (Box 14)
  - Maine State Department, 1950 (Box 14)
  - Minnesota State Department, 1949-1950 (Box 14)
  - North Dakota State Department, 1948-1950 (Box 14)
  - Prairie Farmer, WLS, 1947-1952 (Box 14)
  - Purdue University, 1951-1952 (Box 14)
  - UIR, 1949 (Box 14)
  - University of Nebraska, 1950 (Box 14)
  - WABE-FM, 1950 (Box 14)
  - WAJC, 1950 (Box 14)
  - WANE, (television station), 1950-1951 (Box 14)
  - WAOV, 1947-1950 (Box 14)
  - Warsaw, Indiana University Wilson Junior High School (Muncie), 1948 (Box 14)
  - WASK, 1948-1950 (Box 14)
  - WAVE, (television station), 1947-1948 (Box 14)
  - WBAA (Box 14)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 14)
    - 1946-1954 (Box 14)
  - WBAT, 1949-1950 (Box 14)
  - WBEZ, 1950-1951 (Box 14)
  - WBGO (two folders), 1948-1952 (Box 14)
  - WBIW, 1949-1950 (Box 14)
  - WBOE, 1944-1946 (Box 14)
  - WBOW, 1947-1950 (Box 14)
  - WBOX, 1947-1950 (Box 14)
  - WBSC, 1950 (Box 14)
  - WBUR, 1950 (Box 14)
  - WCAU, (television station), 1953 (Box 14)
  - WCBC, 1948-1950 (Box 14)
  - WCFL, 1948-1950 (Box 14)
  - WCNB, 1947-1950 (Box 14)
  - WCSI (four folders), 1946-1951; 1959 (Box 14)
  - WCTW, 1947-1950 (Box 14)
  - WDTR, 1951 (Box 14)
  - WEOA, 1948-1950 (Box 14)
  - WEPS, 1950 (Box 14)
  - WEVC, 1951-1953 (Box 14)
  - WFAM, 1953 (Box 14)
  - WFBM, 1949-1950 (Box 14)
  - WFIU (Box 14)
    - Completed CP application, 1950 (Box 14)
    - Newsletter, 1950-1951 (Box 14)
    - Reception list, count of, 1947-1950 (Box 14)
    - Station license, 1949-1951 (Box 14)
    - Station plans, 1944-1957 (Box 14)
    - Traffic sheets, 1950 (Box 14)
  - WFJL, 1949-1950 (Box 14)
  - WFML, 1948-1950 (Box 15)
  - WFMU, 1948-1950 (Box 15)
  - WFPL (two folders), 1948-1951 (Box 15)
  - WFTW, 1950 (Box 15)
  - WGBF & WMILL, 1947-1950 (Box 15)
  - WGL, 1950 (Box 15)
  - WGN, (television station), 1947 (Box 15)
  - WGRE, 1950 (Box 15)
  - WHAS (two folders), 1948-1954 (Box 15)
  - WHBU, 1949-1950 (Box 15)
  - WHCU, 1943-1944 (Box 15)
  - WHOT, 1949-1951 (Box 15)
  - WIBC, 1947-1950 (Box 15)
  - WIKY, (television station), 1948-1950 (Box 15)
  - WILL, 1950-1954 (Box 15)
  - Wilson Junior High School (Muncie), 1950 (Box 15)
  - WIMS, 1947-1950 (Box 15)
  - WINN, 1949-1950 (Box 15)
  - WIOU, 1949-1950 (Box 15)
  - WIRE (two folders), 1942-1954 (Box 15)
  - WISH, (television station), 1948-1951 (Box 15)
  - WITZ, 1948-1950 (Box 15)
  - WJJD, 1948 (Box 15)
  - WJOB, 1947-1950 (Box 15)
  - WJPS, 1949-1950 (Box 15)
  - WJVA, 1948-1950 (Box 15)
  - WKAM, 1950 (Box 15)
  - WKBV, 1949-1950 (Box 15)
  - WKEI, 1953 (Box 15)
  - WKJG, 1950 (Box 16)
  - WKLO, 1948-1950 (Box 16)
  - WKMO (two folders), 1948-1950 (Box 16)
  - WKYW, 1948-1950 (Box 16)
  - WLOI, 1949-1950 (Box 16)
  - WLOU, 1949-1950 (Box 16)
  - WLW, 1949-1954 (Box 16)
  - WMAQ, (television station), 1951 (Box 16)
  - WMBI, 1948 (Box 16)
  - WMCR, 1950 (Box 16)
  - WMOK, 1949-1951 (Box 16)
  - WMUN & WLBC, (television stations), 1947-1950 (Box 16)
  - WMRI, 1949-1950 (Box 16)
  - WNAS, 1950-1951 (Box 16)
  - WNAS-FM, 1954 (Box 16)
  - WNEW, 1951 (Box 16)
  - WNYC, 1944-1949 (Box 16)
  - WNYE (two folders), 1949-1950 (Box 16)
  - WORX (Box 16)
    - 1954 (Box 16)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 16)
  - WOWO, 1948-1950 (Box 16)
  - WRSW, 1948-1950 (Box 16)
  - WSAL (two folders), 1950-1951 (Box 16)
  - WSBT, 1948-1950 (Box 16)
  - WSDX, 1950 (Box 16)
  - WSRK (two folders), 1949-1951 (Box 16)
  - WTCJ, 1950 (Box 16)
  - WTDS, (television station), 1950 (Box 16)
  - WTHI, (television station), 1950 (Box 16)
  - WTRC, 1949-1950 (Box 16)
  - WTTM, 1951 (Box 16)
  - WTTS, 1950 (Box 16)
  - WTTV, (television station) (Box 16)
    - 1952-1954 (Box 16)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 16)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 16)
  - WUOA, (television station), 1950 (Box 16)
  - WUOM, 1949-1951 (Box 16)
  - WVLU, 1950 (Box 16)
  - WVSH (two folders), 1949-1952; 1954 (Box 16)
  - WWCA, 1951-1954 (Box 16)
  - WWHI (two folders), 1950 (Box 16)
  - WWNI, 1948-1950 (Box 16)
  - WXLW, 1948-1950 (Box 16)
  - WYSN, 1954 (Box 16)